Hi, welcome to learn and master guitar session seven,
嗨，欢迎来到 learn and master guitar 第七节，
in this session, we're going to cover lots of great important things,
在这节课中，我们将讨论很多重要的东西，
are going to start talking about barre chords,
我们将开始讨论横按和弦，
and until this point we've talked about open chords,
到目前为止，我们已经讨论了开放和弦，
some of your basic chords,
一些你的基本和弦，
in the keys that guitar players personally,
在吉他演奏者个人喜欢的调，
like, C G D A and E,
比如 C G D A 和 E ，
now we're going to start talking about getting into other keys
现在我们将开始讨论进入其他调，
and I'm going to teach you the secret to playing in any key,
我将教你演奏任何调的秘密，
that you ever ask to be playing is barre chords,
你问过的，就是横按和弦，
we're talking about ways to strengthen our fingers,
我们在讨论如何加强我们的手指，
so that our fingers are able to to play the barre chords, like we need to,
让我们的手指能够像我们需要的那样弹奏横按和弦，
a lot of folks complain about they can't get their fingers strong enough,
很多人抱怨他们的手指不够强壮，
so we're going to talk about that a little bit,
所以我们要稍微谈谈这个，
we're also going to learn all of the notes,
我们还将学习所有的音符，
on the entire neck of the guitar on the sixth string,
所有吉他琴颈上第六弦上的音符，
okay, which is the string that we used to pivot off, pivot these barre chords off of.
这是我们用来作为横按和弦[支点]的弦。
We're also going to start a new section,
我们还将开始一个新的部分，
this [DVD] called how music works,
名为音乐是如何工作的，
a little bit about music theory,
有点关于音乐理论，
a little bit about some of the understanding of why music works the way,
有点关于音乐为什么工作的一些理解，
it does first thing we're going to talk about is half steps and whole steps in music,
我们首先要讨论的是音乐中的半音和全音，
going about building a major scale,
如何建立一个主要的音阶，
so we've got an awful lot to cover,
所以我们有很多要涵盖的内容，
I hope you're ready to go,
我希望你们已经准备好了，
let's get started.
让我们开始吧。
Okay, let's talk about barre chords,
好的，让我们来谈谈横按和弦，
barre chords opens up a whole new world for us,
横按和弦为我们打开了一个全新的世界，
as we play guitar,
当我们弹吉他时，
it shifts us from just playing in a couple of keys,
它改变了我们只用几个调演奏，
so now we can play in any key,
现在我们可以用任何调演奏，
and that's what barre chords allow us to do,
这就是横按和弦允许我们做的，
barre chords, let me explain that first of all,
横按和弦，让我先解释一下，
it's not b a r, it's b a r r e,
它不是 b a r ，它是 b a r r e ，
sometimes the spelling you might think we've misspelled things throughout the whole book,
有时候你可能会认为整本书都拼错了，
no, not at all,
不，完全不是，
the barre is b a r r e,
横按是 b a r r e ，
when we get into barre chords,
当我们进入横按和弦的时候，
there's a couple things before we have to get there,
有几件事，
I've got to show you a couple of skills,
我要给你们展示一些技巧，
that you can get your hands strengthened on,
可以加强你的手，
its where you're able to do the barres, when we get to them,
当我们遇到时，可以做到横按，
here in a minute.
在这里一会儿。
First thing we need to talk about is our hand position,
我们首先要讨论的是手的位置，
let's review some of the good things,
让我们回顾一下一些好的事情，
that we need to do with our hand position,
我们需要用手的位置做的（事情），
and this is going to become real critical here,
这将变得非常关键，
as we get into these bigger chords,
当我们现在进入这些更大的和弦，
now before when we're doing our Cs and our Gs and Ams,
在我们做 C G 和 Am 之前，
remember I told you,
记得我告诉你，
we need to have our wrist down,
我们需要手腕向下，
there needs to be air space between our bottom of our wrist or palm,
在我们的手腕底部或手掌需要空间，
the face of our palm and the bottom of the guitar,
手掌表面和吉他底部之间，
you don't want your thumb hanging over the top,
你不想让拇指悬在顶部，
especially when we get to barre chords,
特别是当我们开始横按和弦的时候，
it just doesn't work, when they have it like that,
那样做是不起作用的，
we're going to lower that wrist, bring that first finger out
我们要把手腕放低，把食指伸出来，
and he's going to be straight,
它是笔直的，
this is one of the keys to playing barre chords well,
这是弹好横按和弦的关键之一，
is getting that first finger straight, okay.
就是伸直食指。
Now, bar chords,
横按和弦，
let's talk about the difference between barre chords and movable chords,
让我们讨论一下横按和弦和可移动和弦的区别，
they're they're really the same thing,
它们实际上是一回事，
but barre chords tells you a little bit more about,
但横按和弦告诉你更多，
barre chords mean that, when you barre,
横按和弦意思是，当你横按，
that's telling you that,
这是告诉你，
you're using one finger to cover more than one string,
你用一根手指覆盖不止一根弦，
okay, not all movable chords use barres,
好的，并不是所有可移动的和弦都使用横按，
but for our purposes right now, they will,
但对我们当前的目的来说，它们是的，
so you're covering one,
所以，你覆盖一个，
you're using one finger to cover more than one string,
你用一根手指覆盖不止一根弦，
now, this requires a lot of work for our first finger,
现在，这需要我们的食指做很多工作，
so we're going to have to strengthen him up
所以我们必须加强他的力量，
and we're going to cover that in just a second,
我们将在稍后介绍，
but before that, I need to show you a little bit about,
但在此之前，我需要向你们展示一下，
how we move these chords along the neck,
我们如何沿着琴颈移动这些和弦，
we need to learn all the notes on this six string first,
我们需要首先学习第六弦上的所有音符，
so that when it's time to move those chords,
这样当我们移动这些和弦的时候，
we know where we're moving them to.
我们知道要把它们移动到哪里。
Okay, so let's talk about the six string here for a second.
好的，让我们来讨论一下第六弦。
Need to teach you musical concept called half steps and whole steps,
需要教你的音乐概念，叫做半音和全音，
half steps and whole steps,
半音和全音，
in this big world of ours,
在我们这个大世界里，
half steps are the distance from one note to the next note,
半音是一个音符到下一个音符的距离，
wherever it is,
无论它在哪里，
okay, just whatever the next frets were on a guitar,
无论在吉他上下一个品格，
one fret is a half step,
一个品格就是一个半音，
okay,
好的，
in a piano, if you wanted to put it with piano,
在钢琴上，如果你想把它放在钢琴上，
if you're on a piano,
如果你在钢琴上，
hitting a note
敲击一个音符，
and then the next key whether it's white or black, would be a half step,
然后下一个键，无论是白的还是黑的，都是半音，
just that distance from one note to the next note is a half step,
从一个音符到下一个音符的距离是半音，
if I put two of those together,
如果我把两个放在一起，
I get a whole step.
我就得到一个全音。
So like if I'm down here,
如果我在这里，
the distance between a C and a D would be a whole step,
C 和 D 之间的距离是一个全音，
I'm covering a half step and then another half step,
我先走半音，然后再走半音，
so the distance from a C to a D would be a whole step,
所以从 C 到 D 的距离是一个全音，
an F to a G, that would be a whole step,
从 F 到 G ，也是一个全音，
even when we use an open string,
即使我们用空弦，
there's still this one fret, in between between this G and A,
这里有一个品格，在 G 和 A 之间，
those would also be whole steps.
这也是一个全音。
And half steps are between two pairs of notes,
半音在两个音符之间，
this is very critical,
这是非常关键的，
the only that, here's the rule,
唯一的，规则是，
the only naturally occurring half steps are between E and F and B and C,
唯一自然发生的半音是在 E 和 F ， B 和 C 之间，
naturally occurring, what I mean by that is,
自然发生的，我的意思是，
there's no sharps or flats involved,
没有涉及升调和降调，
if we're not talking about sharps or flats at all,
如果我们完全不谈论升调和降调，
we're just talking about,
我们只是谈论，
just the notes C D E F G and A and B,
只是音符 C D E F G A B，
the only naturally occurring half steps are between two pairs of notes,
唯一自然发生的半音是在两对音符之间，
E and F, and B and C,
E 和 F ， B 和 C ，
on our guitar be E to F and B to C,
在我们的吉他上， E 到 F ， B 到 C ，
now you may think that's not very important,
你可能认为这不是很重要，
but here in a second it's gonna get real critical.
但是稍后，它将变得非常关键。
Let's learn the notes on the sixth string,
我们来学习第六弦上的音符，
we already have open E,
我们已经有了空弦 E ，
we have first finger F,
我们有食指 F ，
we've got up here on the third fret G,
我们在三品上有 G ，
well, if I wanted to keep going higher,
如果我想继续走得更高，
the distance between a G to an A would be a whole step,
从 A 到 G 的距离将是一个全音，
think of it this way,
这样想，
everything is going to be a whole step, except for two pairs of notes,
所有的东西都是一个全音，除了两对音符，
E and F and B and C,
E 和 F ， B 和 C ，
all the other ones without sharps or flats are going to be whole steps,
所有其他的没有升调或降调的音阶都是全音，
so a G to an A would be a whole step,
所以 G 到 A 是一个全音，
and A to a B would be another whole step,
而 A 到 B 是另一个全音，
now here I want to go to a C,
现在我想到 C ，
but the rule says,
但是规则是，
between a B and C is a half step,
在 B 和 C 之间是一个半音，
so that would just be one fret [], that would be C,
所以这只是一个品格[]，那就是 C ，
now we need to go from C to the next note which would be a D,
现在我们需要从 C 到下一个音符 D ，
well, that's not one of our exceptions,
这不是我们的一个例外，
so that would be a whole step again,
所以这将是一个全音，
D to E would be another whole step again,
D 到 E 将是另一个全音，
let's do that again, you try it with me at home.
让我们再来一次，你在家里和我试一下。
We have E F G,
我们有 E F G ，
then the next note would be A,
那么下一个音符将是 A ，
that would be a whole step up, that's the fifth fret,
这将是一个全音，第五品，
next note would be a B,
下一个音符是 B ，
that would be a whole step up, at the seventh fret
是一个全音，在第七品上，
and then between B and C that's just a half step,
然后在 B 和 C 之间，这只是半音，
so that's at the eighth fret,
所以这在第八品，
then D, a whole step above that at ten,
然后 D ，一个全音，在第十品，
and D to E would be our last one up here
而 D 到 E 将是我们这里的最后一个，
and that would be the twelfth fret.
这将是第十二品。
Now let me tell you about the magical twelfth fret,
现在让我告诉你神奇的第十二品，
at the twelfth fret, everything starts repeating,
在第十二品上，一切都开始重复，
this would be E,
这将是 E ，
then you'd have F, just like this F,
然后你会有 F ，就像这个 F ，
then you'd have G, just like this G,
然后你就会有 G ，就像这个 G ，
so just kind of keeps going,
所以就像这样继续，
E F G A B,
E F G A B ，所以真的一旦你得到了前12个，你就有了剩下的乐器，因为它一直在重复，好的，我们再来一次。
so really once you've got the first twelve,
所以一旦你得到了前十二个，
you have the rest of the instrument there,
你就有了剩下的乐器，
because it just keeps repeating.
因为它一直在重复。
Okay, let's do it one more time,
好的，我们再来一次，
E F G A B C D E,
E F G A B C D E ，
now let's go back down backwards,
现在让我们倒退一遍，
okay, try and say and play the notes with me,
好的，试着说出来，和我一起演奏音符，
E D C B A G F E.
E D C B A G F E 。
Very good, now, when I throw sharps or flats in it,
很好，现在，当我在里面加入升调和降调，
I just have to raise,
我只需提高，
remember for whatever note is,
记得无论音符是什么，
if I'm sharpening it, I go up one half step,
如果我升高它，我就会上升半音，
which would be one frets [worth],
将是一个品格[]，
so if I wanted a #G,
所以如果我想要 #G ，
there would be a #G on the fourth fret,
这里将会有 #G 在第四品上，
if I wanted, let's say a #C,
如果我想要 #C ，
that would be,
这将是，
well, here C, I go a half step above that
这里是 C ，我比它高半音，
and I get #G.
我得到了 #C 。
So now let's jump around a little bit,
所以现在我们跳过一点，
I'm just gonna tell you a couple of them
我只告诉你几个，
and you try and find them, okay?
你试着找到它们，好吗？
We'll start out with G,
我们将从 G 开始，
there would be a G,
这是 G ，
what about C, where would that be at,
那么 C 呢，它会在哪里，
counted out, E F G A B C, at the eighth fret,
数一下， E F G A B C ，在第八品中，
what about F,
那么 F 呢，
well, that was pretty easy, that's down here at the first,
这很容易，它在第一品，
one of the first things we learned,
我们第一次学到的东西，
what about a bB now,
那么 bB 呢，
well, here's a B, so there's a bB,
好的，这里是 B ，所以这里是 bB ，
what about an bE,
那么 bE 呢，
well, go up to the twelfth fret,
好的，上升到第十二品，
that's E,
这是 E ，
I can't get any lower down here to the opening,
我不能再往下走了，在空弦上，
so I've gotta go high,
所以我必须升高，
if I can't go low, I've gotta go high,
如果我不能降低，我必须升高，
there's E, there's bE,
这是 E ，这是 bE ，
so there's some, there's some chance for you to practice in there.
所以你有机会在那里练习。
Now, we need to get our first finger strong enough
现在我们需要让我们的食指足够强壮，
to do some of the barre chords that are coming up here in a minute,
来做一些稍后会出现的横按和弦，
so let's talk about strengthening up our first finger.
所以让我们来讨论一下加强食指。
Okay.
好的。
Many people say that barre chords,
很多人说横按 和弦，
they just don't do barre chords,
他们不做横按和弦，
because barre chords are hard.
因为横按和弦很难。
Well, barre chords aren't hard,
好的，横按和弦并不难，
you are just weak,
你只是很弱，
especially your first finger,
特别是你的食指，
well, at least your first finger is weak,
好的，至少你的食指很弱，
so we need to strengthen up that first finger a little bit,
所以我们需要稍微加强一下你的食指，
before we get into barre chords,
在我们进入横按和弦之前，
so let's go up to here, the fifth fret,
所以让我们来看看第五品，
okay,
好的，
and we'll put our first finger down
我们把食指放下，
and we're going to cover three strings at a time,
我们一次覆盖三根弦，
just the bottom three strings,
最后三根弦，
okay, with our first finger,
好的，用我们的食指，
play those,
弹奏它们，
I put it down, I gotta put a lot more pressure on this
我把它放下来，我要加大压力，
and we play all three of them together,
我们弹奏所有三根弦，
ready, let's play,
准备，我们弹奏，
now it may buzz a little bit
现在它可能会嗡嗡作响，
as your fingers getting used to,
随着你的手指习惯于，
strengthening up to do to play these barre chords,
加强来演奏这些横按和弦，
but that's okay,
但没关系，
that's what we're trying to strengthen right now,
这就是我们现在正在努力加强的，
it takes a while to do this,
这需要一段时间来做，
you may not be getting this the first time you do it,
你可能不会在第一次这样做时就感觉到这一点，
it takes a while to get your fingers strengthened up enough
需要一段时间才能让你的手指足够强壮
to do what we need to do,
来做我们需要做的事情，
so let's just go through a little exercise to help you,
所以让我们来做一些小练习来帮助你，
make sure you have good hand position,
确保你有良好的手部位置，
make sure that wrist is forward,
确保手腕是向前的，
not back like this, but forward
不是像这样向后，而是向前，
and your finger is straight,
并且你的手指是直的，
finger straight on the frets,
手指直的放在品格上，
okay, make sure that first finger is dead straight,
好的，确保食指是笔直的，
not angling in a little bit like this,
而不是像这样稍微倾斜，
I know you need pressure
我知道你需要施压，
and you want to bring that wrist up for pressure,
你想把手腕抬起来施压，
leave that wrist down for that,
把手腕降下来，
okay, try not to buzz.
好的，试着不要嗡嗡作响。
Let's go over the fifth, fifth fret, cover three strings,
让我们复习一下第五品，覆盖三根弦，
okay, now let's take the whole picture down,
好的，现在让我们把整个画面记录下来，
let's go down to the third fret,
让我们继续第三品，
so you can get those three,
这样你就可以得到这三个，
good,
好的，
let's jump down to maybe the second fret,
让我们跳到第二品，
the closer I get to this nut down here though,
我越接近这个琴枕，
it gets a little bit harder,
它变得更困难，
the easiest place to practice these barre chords in the middle of the neck
最容易练习这些横按和弦的位置是在琴颈的中间，
right here at the fifth or the seventh fret,
在第五品或第七品，
what about at the first fret,
那么在第一品呢，
can you get all those three to sound.
你能让这三个都发声吗。
Okay, now let's do four strings,
好的，现在我们来做四根弦，
okay, let's go back up here to the fifth fret
好的，让我们回到第五品，
and now we're going to do four strings,
现在我们来做四根弦，
okay, trying to get those to sound,
好的，试着让这些发声，
let's go up, maybe the seventh fret,
让我们向上，也许是第七品，
let's go up a little bit more, what about if the ninth fret here.
让我们再向上一点，这里的第九品。
Good, alright, now let's kick it up a notch,
好的，现在让我们把它提升一个档次，
let's go to five strings,
让我们到五根弦，
okay, now you don't want your finger necessarily straight on the instrument like this,
好的，你不想让你的手指像这样直直地放在乐器上，
you want it kind of angled a little bit,
你想让它有点倾斜，
I mean if you can kind of see where my finger,
我是说，如果你能看到我的手指在哪里，
the, the notches in my finger,
我手指上的凹槽，
where the strings are really on this last quarter of my finger,
弦在我手指的最后四分之一上，
so I'm not necessarily dead on,
所以我不一定完全准确，
I'm kind of offset a little bit.
我稍微有点偏向。
Let's go over here to the third fret and do the same thing,
让我们到第三品，做同样的事情，
remember a good good finger position,
记住一个好的手指位置，
if I'm hugging up right behind the fret,
如果我紧跟在品丝后面，
that's the easiest place for me to get the notes to sound,
这是最容易让音符发出声音的地方，
requires the least amount of pressure,
需要最小的压力，
okay, if I'm back here going to sound real buzzy.
好的，如果我回到这里，听起来真的很嗡嗡作响。
Okay, let's go down to the first fret, it's pretty tough down there.
好的，让我们到第一品，那里很难。
Okay, now let's go to all six, okay,
好的，现在让我们去全部六根弦，
now you got a little, take a little practice
现在你需要做一点练习，
to figure out where you actually need to push that first finger down at,
找出你真正需要按下食指的地方，
it might help to actually overshoot,
超过可能会帮助你，
you don't want to be just right here,
你不想在这里，
it helps to kind of overshoot a little bit,
超过一点有所帮助，
I kind of overshoot it, I don't know maybe a half an inch or so,
我有点超过可能半英寸左右，
so you can get all six strings,
所以你可以得到所有六根弦，
each string to sound out of a clear sound,
每根弦发出清晰的声音，
let's go down to the third fret,
让我们降到第三品，
and eventually down to the first fret,
最终降到第一品，
if you can conquer,
如果你能克服，
putting all the pressure that you need
给出你需要的所有压力，
to get that first fret, all six strings without buzzing,
让第一品所有六根线不会嗡嗡作响，
you've got enough strength to do any barre chord, that I'm gonna be able to throw at you.
你有足够的力量来做任何我给你的横按和弦。
Okay, so you may not be able to do this initially,
好的，所以你可能一开始不能这样做，
so take a little bit of time each day,
所以每天花一点时间，
strengthen up that first finger,
加强你的食指，
don't give up after the first time you do it,
不要在第一次做完之后放弃，
it takes a little, it takes a little bit of time
它需要一点时间，
over a couple of weeks maybe,
可能在几周内，
to get that first finger strengthened up enough.
让食指足够强壮。
Okay, ready to learn some barre chords,
好的，准备好学习一些横按和弦，
let's go ahead and do that.
让我们继续学习。
Okay, let's talk about five major chord forms,
好的，让我们讨论五种主要的和弦形式，
that we're going to learn on that six string.
我们将在第六根弦上学习的。
Okay, now you'll notice,
好的，现在你会注意到，
as we put up the first one, the F chord,
我们放第一个和弦， F 和弦，
okay, that you're going,
好的，你要，
there's a couple of new concepts that you're going to see on that chord block,
你会在和弦上看到一些新的概念，
that you haven't seen before yet,
你以前没有见过的，
first one of them is a fret number,
它们中的第一个是品数，
okay, everything up to this point,
好的，到目前为止，
we've done down here in the first position,
我们已经做了第一把位，
but now you're gonna start seeing a fret number beside some of your chord forms,
但现在你会开始看到一些和弦形式旁边的品数，
which would be a 1fr.,
它是 1fr. ，
sometimes it may say 5fr.,
有时它可能是 5fr. ，
which would be like the fifth fret,
就是第五品，
or the seventh fret, 7fr.,
或第七品， 7fr. ，
that's just telling you the fret number that you're at.
告诉你所在的品数。
Okay, the other thing is
好的，另一件事是，
you're going to see that big arc over the top of it,
你会看到它顶部的大弧线，
that is the symbol for a barre,
这是横按的符号，
that means everything that is covered there,
这意味着那里的所有东西覆盖，
is being covered by that one finger,
都被那根手指覆盖，
sometimes that barre will be just two strings,
有时横按只有两根弦，
sometimes it'll be four,
有时它是四根，
in all of these that we're doing today,
在我们今天要做的所有这些东西中，
it's going to be all six strings.
它将是所有的六根弦。
The last one, you'll notice there's a diamond,
最后一个，你会注意到，这里有一个钻石符号，
we don't have just black circles and open circles,
我们不只有黑色的圆圈和开放的圆圈，
now weve got a diamond in there,
现在我们在那里有一个钻石符号，
that diamond is critical,
这个钻石符号是关键的，
that's going to be the note that we're pivoting off of,
这是我们转到的音符，
as we're moving these chords around,
我们会移动这些和弦，
we'll talk a little bit more about that later,
我们稍后会更多地讨论这个问题，
but that's the note that we're pivoting off of.
但这是我们要转到的音符。
Okay, first we're going to learn is an F chord.
好的，首先我们要学习的是 F 和弦。
Okay, so let's see what we've got here,
好的，让我们看看和弦上有什么，
on that chord block,
在和弦块上，
you'll notice the first, there's a barre over those six strings,
你会注意到，第一，有一个横按在六根弦上，
okay, so you get that happening first,
所以你先弹这个，
then you put your third finger on that fifth string F,
然后你把无名指放在第五弦 F 上，
pinky underneath that,
小拇指在它下面，
and then that A is covered by the second finger on the third string,
然后 A 被中指按在第三弦上，
that's an F chord.
这是 F 和弦。
Let's try one more time,
让我们再试一次，
make sure each note is sounding out nice and clearly,
确保每个音符听起来都很好听和清晰，
again, it takes a while to get this,
需要一段时间才能得到这个，
so if you don't get it the first time,
所以如果你第一次没有得到，
don't give up,
不要放弃，
it takes a while to strengthen your muscles,
它需要一段时间来加强你的肌肉，
the only difference between this and this is hand strength,
这个和这个的唯一的区别是手的力量，
I didn't move the position of my fingers at all,
我根本没有移动手指的位置，
so if your chord sounds more like this,
所以如果你的和弦听起来更像这样，
all it takes is a little bit more hand strength to get it
你只需要多一点手的力量就可以得到它，
and you'll be doing it,
你就可以完成它，
okay, there's an F.
好的，这是 F 。
Now, the next form, we're going to learn is
我们要学习的下一个形式是，
an F minor, Fm you'll see,
F 小调，你看到的 Fm ，
then I just take my second finger off,
我只是把我的食指拿开，
and I've got an Fm.
我就得到了 Fm 。
Next one is an F7,
下一个是 F7 ，
I put my second finger back on,
我把我的中指放回去，
I take my pinky off
我拿开小拇指，
and that's an F7.
那就是 F7 。
The fourth one down there
下面的第四个，
or the fourth one we're going to cover is an Fm7,
也就是我们要讲的第四个是 Fm7 ，
I take my second finger off and my pinky off.
我把中指和小拇指拿掉。
And then the last one is an Fsus,
最后一个是 Fsus ，
which I put my pinky back on,
我把我的小拇指放回去，
except this time I put him down on the third string.
但这次把他放在第三弦上。
Okay, so those are the five chord forms that we're going to talk about.
好的，这是我们要讨论的五种和弦形式。
Okay.
好的。
Now, let's talk about moving those chord forms,
现在让我们讨论一下如何移动这些和弦形式，
if you look at the first example in your book,
如果你看书中的第一个例子，
you've got an F chord,
你有一个 F 和弦，
so for, let's form an F chord
我们组成一个 F 和弦，
and then it goes up to a G chord,
然后它上升到 G 和弦，
well, here's where the pivoting comes in place,
这就是移动的地方，
remember how I taught you half steps and whole steps
记得我是如何教你半音和全音的，
and learning what notes they are on the sixth string,
学习在第六弦上是什么音符，
if I take this F chord,
如果我用这个 F 和弦，
where's the F in this F chord,
这个 F 和弦中的 F 在哪里，
as far as a six string is concerned,
就六根弦而言，
it's right here, on my first finger,
它在这里，在我的食指上，
if I move my first finger to where G is
如果我把我的食指移动到 G 的位置，
and now form the exact same chord,
现在形成相同的和弦，
I've got A G chord,
我就得到了一个 G 和弦，
see how that works,
看到它是如何工作的，
the next measure has an A chord,
下一小节有一个 A 和弦，
well, again I put my first finger where the A is
我把我的食指放到 A 所在的地方，
and then form the chord down I've got A.
然后形成和弦，我得到了 A 。
Next one is a bB,
下一个是降B ，
I go up here to bB,
我到这里降B ，
I do the whole chord.
我做了整个和弦。
So if I was doing all that together,
所以如果我把所有这些都放在一起，
it would be like this,
就会像这样，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
F, two three four,
F 2 3 4 ，
then move up to G, two three four,
然后上升到 G 2 3 4 ，
A, two three four
A 2 3 4 ，
and bB, two three four,
然后，降B 2 3 4 。
very good.
非常好。
Okay, now let's move on to the next one,
好的，现在让我们进入下一个，
just, just between a couple of these forms,
就在这几个形式之间，
we've got, it starts out on a G,
我们从 G 开始，
we find our G, we make our chord,
我们找到 G ，弹奏我们的和弦，
okay, then it goes to Am,
好的，然后切换到 Am ，
so we have to go up here to A,
我们到 A ，
form Am chord,
形成 Am 和弦，
and it goes to Bm
它到达 Bm ，
and C.
以及 C 。
Okay, very good,
好的，非常好，
that gives some idea of barre chords
这给出了一些横按和弦的概念，
and how you move them.
以及你如何移动它们。
Now it's going to take you a while to get these,
现在你需要一段时间才能拿到这些，
so I know I ran through pretty quick,
我知道我很快就讲完了，
that's why the workshop time is going to start paying off here,
这就是为什么 workshop 时间会开始有回报的原因，
now let's learn a little bit about music in our how music works section.
现在让我们在音乐工作原理部分学习一些关于音乐的知识。
Okay, welcome to our how music works section,
好的，欢迎来到我们的音乐原理部分，
learning a little bit about music and a little bit how music fits together
了解一点音乐和音乐是如何结合在一起的，
is one of the most important skills that you can learn as a guitar player.
是作为一个吉他演奏者可以学到的最重要的技能之一。
So maybe thinking, gosh, just teach me a couple of chords
所以，也许会想，天哪，只要教我几个和弦，
and I'm ready to go,
我就准备好了，
well, that's maybe the learn part of the learn and master guitar,
这可能是 learn and master guitar 的学习部分，
but the part of when you get into the master part of it,
但当你进入它的掌握部分，
you need to learn a little bit about music
你需要学习一些关于音乐的知识，
and about how music affects your playing as a guitar player,
以及音乐如何影响你作为吉他演奏者的演奏，
so we're going to take a second to learn a little bit about that.
所以我们将花一点时间来了解一下。
The road to all, learning how chords are spelled what notes
通向所有学习和弦如何拼写音符，
and how we can move those chords around,
以及如何移动这些和弦，
it all starts with major scales
都是从大调音阶开始的，
and major scales are built up of half steps and whole steps,
大调音阶是由半音和全音组成的，
we talked about half steps a little bit previously,
我们之前说过半音，
okay, half step is distance between one note and his immediate neighbour,
半音是一个音符和它的直接邻居之间的距离，
okay, I get two half steps, I put them together, I get a whole step,
好的，我把两个半音放在一起，我得到一个全音，
right, remember the rule,
记住规则，
the only naturally occurring half steps are between E and F and B and C,
唯一自然出现的半音是在 E 和 F ， B 和 C 之间，
the only naturally occurring half steps are between E and F and B and C.
唯一自然发生的半音是在 E 和 F ， B 和 C 之间。
Okay, but when we start to add things in here,
好的，但是当我们开始在这里加东西的时候，
you need to keep track of those sharps and flats,
你需要跟踪那些升调和降调，
as you'll see,
你会看到，
okay, so if the distance between F and G is a whole step,
所以如果 F 和 G 之间的距离是一个全音，
then the distance from an #F to #G is also a whole step,
那么从 #F 到 #G 的距离也是一个全音，
if an F to G is a whole step,
如果 F 到 G 是一个全音，
an #F to #G is a whole step.
那么 #F 到 #G 也是一个全音。
Okay, see how that works,
好的，看到它是如何工作的，
let's do a couple of examples real quick,
让我们快速地做几个例子，
what's the distance from a #C to a D,
从 #C 到 D 的距离是多少，
now, if you want to play this on your guitar,
如果你想在你的吉他上演奏，
that's fine too,
也没问题，
if you want to think about it in music,
如果你想在乐谱中考虑它，
which is what we're going to put on the screen,
这就是我们要放在屏幕上的，
I want you to think about in music notation too,
我希望你们也考虑一下乐谱，
because this is true,
因为这是正确的，
no matter whether you're playing a guitar or piano or trumpet or tuba.
无论你是在弹吉他、钢琴、小号还是大号。
Okay, the distance between a #C and D is a half step,
好的， #C 和 D 之间的距离是半音，
a C to a D is a whole step,
C 到 D 是一个全音，
I've moved that C closer to the D,
我把 C 移近 D ，
now, #C to a D is just a half step.
#C 到 D 只有半音。
Okay.
好的。
What is the distance from an bE to an F,
从 bE 到 F 的距离是多少，
think about that for a second,
稍微想一下，
an bE to an F,
bE 到 F ，
if E and F is a half step,
如果 E 和 F 是半音，
then if I scoot that E farther from that F a half step,
那么如果我把 E 移开，离 F 更远半音，
then it becomes an bE
然后变成 bE ，
and that then becomes a whole step,
然后变成一个全音，
so an bE to an f is a whole step.
所以 bE 到 F 是一个全音。
What about the distance from a G to an bA,
G 到 bA 的距离是多少，
well, G to an A is a whole step,
好的，从 G 到 A 是一个全音，
if I scoot that A closer down to that G,
如果我移动 A 到 G 更近的地方，
it becomes just a half step,
它就变成了半音，
so a G to an bA is a half step.
所以 G 到 bA 是一个半音。
Now let's talk about major scales,
现在让我们来谈谈大调音阶，
everything that we're talking about from this point on,
我们从这一点开始讨论的所有东西，
all the theory, all the harmony stuff,
所有理论，所有和声的东西，
what notes you can add the chords to sound hip and and colorful in your sound,
你可以添加哪些音符来使你的声音听起来时髦和丰富多彩，
it is all based off of one thing, major scales,
这些都是基于一个东西，大调音阶。
okay, major scales are the building blocks for all of music
大调音阶是所有音乐的基础，
and they are built from a specific pattern of half steps and whole steps,
它们是从半音和全音的特定模式建立起来的，
it's like math, it's like a formula,
就像数学一样，就像一个公式，
I know many of you math may not have been your best subject,
我知道你们中的许多人数学可能不是最好的学科，
but music has a lot to do with math,
但音乐与数学有很大关系，
in fact some, many studies have found that,
事实上，许多研究发现，
if you have a student that's struggling in math,
如果你有一个在数学上有困难的学生，
if you teach the music,
如果你教音乐，
something about the order and the presentation of the music helps them in their math skills,
一些关于顺序，音乐的呈现有助于他们的数学技能，
so something about that in our brains,
所以在我们的大脑中，
connects the two together in the same way we process the information.
将两者联系在一起，以同样的方式处理信息。
Okay, major scales are built from a pattern,
好的，大调音阶是从一个模式建立起来的，
it's a pattern of half steps and whole steps,
这是一个关于半音和全音的模式，
you're ready for the pattern,
你已经准备好了吗，
here it is,
这就是它，
the pattern for a major scale is
大调音阶的模式是，
whole step, whole step, half step, whole step, whole step, whole step, half step,
全音，全音，半音，全音，全音，全音，半音，
okay, so it's two whole steps and half step, three whole steps and half step,
好的，所以它是两个全音，一个半音，三个全音，一个半音，
that's how a major scale is made,
这就是大调音阶的制作方法，
you start on any note,
你可以从任何音符开始，
whether it's F or G or bB or bG,
无论是它是 F G bB bG ，
you start on that note and you build up,
你从这个音符开始，开始构建，
just like in building blocks,
就像构建块一样，
half step, or you building the half step whole step pattern,
半音，或者你建立半音全音模式，
two wholes and a half, three wholes and a half
两个全音，一个半音，三个全音，一个半音，
and you end up with the major scale.
你最终得到的是大调音阶。
Let's try this a little bit,
让我们试一试这个，
let's start in C,
让我们从 C 开始，
okay, so if I have a C major scale,
好的，如果我有 C 大调音阶，
C, I start on a C,
C ，我从 C 开始，
then the pattern says, I need to go up a whole step,
然后模式说，我需要上升一个全音，
the distance from a C to a D is a whole step,
从 C 到 D 的距离是一个全音，
so I would just go right up to D,
所以我会直接到 D ，
then I need another whole step,
然后我需要另一个全音，
a D to an E is a whole step,
从 D 到 E 是一个全音，
then I need a half step, the pattern says,
然后我需要一个半音，
E to an F conveniently is a half step,
E 到 F 就是一个半音，
next one I need a whole step,
下一步我需要一个全音，
whole step up from an F would be a G,
从 F 开始的全音是 G ，
whole step up from a G would be an A,
从 G 的全音是 A ，
whole step up from an A would be a B,
从 A 的全音是 B ，
and then I have a half step at the end
然后我在最后有一个半音，
and which gets me back to C,
这让我回到 C ，
your first and your last note should always match,
你的第一个音符和最后一个音符应该总是匹配的，
okay, if you get to the end of some of these exercises in,
如果到一些练习的结尾，
your first and last note don't match,
你的第一个和最后一个音符不匹配，
somewhere you screwed up along the way,
有某个地方搞砸了，
the first and last note should always match,
第一个和最后一个音符应该总是匹配，
two wholes and a half, three wholes and a half.
两个全音，一个半音，三个全音，一个半音。
Okay, now as you go through different notes,
好的，当你读不同的音符时，
you need to edit the sharps and flats,
你需要[编辑]升调和降调，
you need to adjust those sharps and flats,
你需要调整那些升调和降调，
in order to make the pattern work out right,
以使模式正确工作，
okay, so we can get the pattern of half steps and whole steps to make a major scale,
我们可以得到半音和全音的模式来做一个大调音阶，
now when you're spelling scales,
现在，当你拼写音阶时，
all of the notes need to be consecutive,
所有的音符都需要是连续的，
what do I mean by that,
我的意思是，
you can't jump from a #C to an E,
你不能 #C 跳到 E ，
I gotta have a note in between,
我得在中间加一个音符，
it has to go A B C D E F G,
它必须是 A B C D E F G ，
I can't jump from a C,
我不能从 C 跳到，
no matter whether it's a #C to an bE,
不论是 #C 到 bE ，
it doesn't, in in music theory that doesn't work,
在音乐理论中，这不是不起作用的，
you can't do that,
你不能这样做，
I have to go from some kind of a C,
我必须从某个 C ，
no matter how bad I have to sharp or flat it
无论我不得不对它升调或降调，
to some kind of a D,
到某个 D ，
no matter bad, no matter how much I have to sharp or flat,
无论我必须升调或降调，
in order for it to work.
才能使它奏效。
Okay, let's try a couple of one,
好的，让我们试几个，
let's try a scale,
我们试一个音阶，
that was going to include some sharps or flats in it,
包括一些升调或降调，
let's try an f scale.
我们来试试 F 音阶。
Okay, we're going to an F major scale,
好的，我们要用 F 大调音阶，
you just think with me, we start on F,
你和我一起想，我们从 F 开始，
and we need a whole step,
我们需要一个全音，
whole step up from an F is a G,
从 F 的一个全音是 G ，
and we need another whole step,
我们还需要一个全音，
whole step up from G is an A,
从 G 的一个全音是 A ，
now I need a half step,
现在我需要一个半音，
here's the trick
这是技巧，
and A to a B as a whole step,
A 到 B 是一个全音，
so I've got to squeeze that B down a half step,
我要把 B 向下调半音，
to get it, to work out in our pattern right,
让它在我们的模式中工作，
whole whole half,
全音，全音，半音，
so it would be F G A and now bB.
所以它应该是 F G A ，现在是 bB 。
Okay, now I need to go a whole step up,
好的，现在我需要上升一个全音，
but I'm going a whole step up from a bB,
但我要 bB 上升一个全音，
so that would be C,
所以是 C ，
if a B to a C is just a half step,
B 到 C 只是半音，
a bB to a C now would be a whole step,
bB 到 C 是一个全音，
and a whole step up from a C is a D,
从 C 的全音是 D ，
whole step up from a D is an E,
从 D 的全音是 E ，
now I'm back to half step, E to an F,
现在我又回到了半音， E 到 F ，
my first and last notes match,
我的第一个音符和最后一个音符匹配，
I've got an F major scale,
我有一个 F 大调，
F G A bB C D E F.
F G A bB C D E F 。
Okay, there are much more exercise,
好的，还有更多的练习，
there are many more exercises in your book
你的书中有更多的练习，
to get you a lot of good practice on major scales,
让你在大调音阶上得到很多好的练习，
it's not just about spelling them once, it's about learning,
这不仅仅是一次拼写，这是关于学习的，
it's kind of like your multiplication tables,
就像你的乘法表，
you're eventually gonna have to learn all these scales,
你最终将不得不学习所有的音阶，
now you may think there's no way I could learn all these scales,
现在你可能会认为我不可能学习所有的音阶，
it's not like there's a hundred of them,
不是说有一百个音符，
there's only twelve different notes on your guitar before they start repeating,
在它们开始重复之前，你的吉他上只有 12 个不同的音符，
so there's only twelve different major scales,
所以只有 12 个不同的大调音阶，
it's not an unknowable amount of information,
这不是一个不可知的信息量，
it's actually a pretty relatively easy amount of information,
这实际上是一个相当容易的信息量，
but it is going to take more than just doing it once,
但它需要做的不仅仅是一次，
so you need to do them over and over and over again,
所以你需要一遍又一遍地做，
that's why we give you plenty of exercises to do that.
这就是为什么我们给你很多练习来做这个。
Okay, so memorize which scales have which sharps and flats,
好的，记住哪些音阶有哪些升调和降调，
that will be a good place for you to start.
这对你来说是一个很好的起点。
Learning how to build scales is one of the most important things you can do for your musicianship,
学习如何建立音阶对你的音乐事业是最重要的事情之一，
it may be a little technical right now,
现在可能有点技术上的问题，
that this is going to start paying off,
这将开始得到回报，
when we start going beyond what the average guitar player can do,
当我们开始超越一般吉他演奏者的能力时，
most every guitar player that you run across can do C and G,
你遇到的几乎每个吉他演奏者都会弹奏 C 和 G ，
well, we're moving beyond C and G now,
我们现在已经超越了 C 和 G ，
we're moving down to playing bA and bG
我们开始弹奏 bA 和 bG ，
and knowing what chords go with what.
知道和什么和弦搭配。
Okay, so if you're finding it,
好的，如果你找到，
where we're going a little bit past you,
我们要去的地方，
go back and review some of the earlier exercises
回顾一些早期的练习，
and we can, get yourself up on those skills,
我们可以，让你自己掌握这些技能，
when we're, now we're building scales, we're ready to go.
现在我们要构建音阶，我们准备开始。
Let's talk about our assignment for this week or for this session,
让我们来谈谈本周或这节课的作业，
let's take a look at our assignment.
让我们来看看我们的作业。
Your assignment for this session is
这节课的作业是
to practice saying and playing the notes on the sixth string
练习发音和弹奏第六弦的音符，
ascending and descending,
向上和向下，
remember how we did that,
记得我们是如何做的，
E F G A B C D E
E F G A B C D E ，
and then I want to say and play them down, E D C B,
然后我想向下发音和弹奏， E D C B 。
okay, all the way down.
一直下来。
Memorize the five six string barre forms that we talked about,
记住我们所说的五个六弦横按形式，
F, Fm, Fm7, F7 and Fsus,
F Fm Fm7 F7 Fsus ，
okay, do those fingering strengthening exercises,
做那些指法强化练习，
if you're having problems getting the barres down to be a strong enough,
如果你有横按力量不足的问题，
okay, try not to get any buzzes or miss notes,
尽量不要发出任何嗡嗡声或错过音符，
okay, play through the six string barre chord exercises in your book,
弹奏书中的第六弦横按和弦练习，
play through the song that we have in our book.
弹奏我们在书中的歌曲。
And for our how music work section,
对于我们的音乐工作部分，
fill out the major scale worksheets in the book,
填写书中的大调音阶工作表，
using the major scale pattern that we talked about,
使用我们讨论过的大调音阶模式，
that's a lot of material for this time,
这一次的材料很多，
but I know you're gonna get it, keep working at it,
但我知道你会继续努力的，
I'll see you at the workshop time.
我们在研讨会上再见。
Hi, welcome to session seven the workshop time,
嗨，欢迎来到第七节课 workshop 时间，
you're ready to work out all the things we learn,
你准备好练习我们学到的东西了，
here we go,
我们开始，
first thing we need to talk about is,
我们首先要说的是，
we're going to jump around on that six string,
我们要在第六弦上跳动，
you jump with me,
你和我一起，
play a G on that six string,
在第六弦上弹 G ，
okay, what about a C,
好的， C 怎么样，
where would that be,
它会在哪里，
it's counted up, E F G A B C,
数一下， E F G A B C ，
let's do that,
让我们做，
let's go, we're gonna count them all the way up and all the way down,
我们来数它们向上并向下，
okay, here we starts on the E F G A B C D E,
好的，我们开始， E F G A B C D E ，
magical twelve fret, okay a lot of guitars have a double dot right there,
神奇的第十二品，很多吉他都有两个点在那里，
going back down, D C B A G F E.
往下， D C B A G F E 。
Let's jump around, find a G,
让我随意弹奏，找一个 G ，
find a C,
找一个 C ，
what about an F,
如果是 F ，
bB,
bB ，
bE, remember you can't go low so you gotta go high,
bE ，记住，你不能往低处走，所以你要往高处走，
twelve fret E, bE,
十二品是 E ， bE ，
bA,
bA ，
#C,
#C ，
#F,
#F ，
B,
B ，
E,
E ，
open E, of course twelve fret,
空弦 E ，当然第十二品，
A,
A ，
D,
D ，
and we're back to C.
我们又回到 C 。
Very good,
很好，
all right now, remember our five forms that we've learned,
记得我们学到的五种形式，
we've learned F,
我们学到了 F ，
take that second finger off, Fm,
把食指拿开，就是 Fm ，
F7,
F7 ，
Fm7,
Fm7 ，
Fsus.
Fsus 。
Okay, remember to have good form,
好的，记住要保持良好的姿势，
lower that wrist, lots of air space in between that,
手腕以下，有很多空间，
keep that first finger straight,
保持食指伸直，
if you need to strengthen up that first finger,
如果你需要加强食指，
take a few seconds, a few minutes to do our finger strengthening exercise, to do that,
花几分钟做手指强化练习，
we're going to go ahead and move on,
我们将继续前进，
but if you need to strengthen that first finger,
但如果你需要加强食指，
do that,
那就去吧，
and come back to us.
然后回来加入我们。
Okay, let's start the basic barre chord exercises,
好的，让我们开始基本的横按和弦练习，
number one,
第一个，
ready play,
准备，开始，
two three four,
2 3 4 ，
repeat it, back down to F.
向下重复，回到 F 。
Number two, G,
第二个， G ，
ready, let's do this one slow
准备，让我们慢一点，
and then we'll play it speed up,
然后我们再演奏快一点，
one time slow, one time fast,
慢一次，快一次，
G, number two, go,
G ，第二个，开始，
one two, another one,
1 2 ，另一个，
Am,
Am ，
Bm,
Bm ，
C.
C 。
And now let's play a little faster,
现在让我们弹得快一点，
ready go,
准备，开始，
G,
G ，
Am
Am ，
try not to hesitate between chords,
试着在和弦之间不要犹豫，
Bm.
Bm 。
Let's skip down and do number four,
让我们跳下去，做第四个，
number four starts on a bB major,
第四个从 bB 大调开始，
you ready, got it,
你准备好了吗，明白了吗，
first time slow,
第一次慢一点，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
Cm,
Cm ，
F7,
F7 ，
big jump down to F7,
很大的跳跃到 F7 ，
Gm,
Gm ，
Cm,
Cm ，
Fsus,
Fsus ，
F7,
F7 ，
bB.
bB 。
Good,
好的，
now, let's try number six,
现在让我们试试第六个，
to close this section off.
来结束这一部分。
Okay, number six starts on a G,
好的，第六个从 G 开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
two,
2 ，
Bm,
Bm ，
big jump up to Bm,
一个大的跳跃到 Bm ，
C,
C ，
back to Bm,
回到 Bm ，
try not to hesitate between chords,
试着不要在和弦之间犹豫，
Am,
Am ，
big jump down to F,
一个大的跳跃到 F ，
#F,
#F ，
two three four.
2 3 4 。
Very good,
非常好，
okay, now let's look at the song, that we have in our book,
好的，现在让我们来看看书中的歌曲，
Home On The Range.
Home On The Range 。
Okay, since three four time,
好的，是三四拍，
let's do the single notes first
我们先弹奏单音符，
and then we'll work on the chords
然后再弹奏和弦，
and I want you to play those chords,
我想让你演奏那些和弦，
even though a lot of them are open chords,
尽管其中很多是开放和弦，
I want you to try and play as many of them as you can, as a barre chord,
我希望你试着尽可能多地作为横按和弦演奏它们，
the idea to strengthen up that hand.
加强那只手。
Okay, let's do the single notes first,
好的，让我们先弹单音，
okay, ready, go,
好的，准备，开始，
eighth notes,
八分音符，
the tie over, three, one two,
延音线， 3 ， 1 2 ，
one two,
1 2 ，
dotted quarter,
加附点的四分音符，
two three, one,
2 3 ， 1 ，
next part, G, two three,
下一部分， G ， 2 3 ，
two three, one two,
2 3 ， 1 2 ，
two three, one two three.
2 3 ， 1 2 3 。
Good, now let's go through the barre chords on it,
好的，现在让我们来看看上面的横按和弦，
okay, when should start on that C,
好的，什么时候开始 C ，
okay,
好的，
the C, where would that C major be,
C 大调在哪里，
well, F G A B C,
好的， F G A B C ，
the first chord is a C major,
第一个和弦是 C 大调，
then it would be a C major again in the next measure,
然后在下一个小节中，它将再次是 C 大调，
even though it's not written,
即使它没有写出来，
then it goes to an F major,
然后它变成 F 大调，
you gotta jump all the way down to F,
你必须一直跳到 F ，
another F,
另一个 F ，
back to C,
回到 C ，
another C,
另一个 C ，
here comes a G7,
这里有一个 G7 ，
jump down to G get the seventh form, two three,
跳到 G ，得到第七形式， 2 3 ，
backup to C, two three,
回到 C ， 2 3 ，
F, go, two three,
F ，开始， 2 3 ，
back to C,
回到 C ，
you get a lot of good practice jumping,
你得到了很多很好的跳跃练习，
two three, two three,
2 3 ， 2 3 ，
here go to the next part G,
继续下一个部分， G ，
G7 now take that pinky off,
G7 ，把小拇指拿开，
C,
C ，
Am,
Am ，
D7, way up here at the top,
D7 ，在这里，
and G,two three,
G ， 2 3 ，
G7,
G7 ，
C,
C ，
back to F,
回到 F ，
Fm there you go,
Fm ，干得不错，
C,
C ，
G7,
G7 ，
back to C,
回到 C ，
two three, one two three.
2 3 ， 1 2 3 。
Very good, good workout on our hands,
非常好，我们的手锻炼得很好，
your hands probably pretty sore about now,
你的手现在可能很酸痛，
I think I might do my little finger exercise here
我想我可以在这里做小的手指练习，
to strengthen up, to loosen up that hand a bit after doing all that.
以加强，在做完所有这些之后放松一下手。
Okay, barre chords take consistent practice,
好的，横按和弦需要持续的练习，
we haven't had a,
我们没有，
it's been a few sessions
已经有几节课了，
since we've actually had to deal with something physical, a physical issue
我们不得不处理一些身体上的问题，
and getting your hand strengthened up enough
让你的手足够强壮
to do barre chords is a physical thing
来做横按和弦是一件身体上的事情，
and it takes time for the average student
对于一般的学生来说，
to get these barre chords down,
按下横按和弦，
like you need to it takes about three weeks,
大约需要三个星期，
so don't feel discouraged,
所以，不要觉得气馁，
if I'm running through real quick
我讲得很快，
and you don't get them in the first ten minutes,
你在前十分钟内没有完成，
it takes about three weeks
这需要大约三个星期，
have given about five or ten minutes each day to toughen up that finger
每天五到十分钟来锻炼手指，
and get him strong enough to do what he needs to,
让它足够强壮，做它需要做的事情，
you can't just do it for a couple hours
你不能只做几个小时，
and be there generally takes a little bit longer than that,
通常需要更长的时间，
so don't be discouraged, when you do that.
所以当你这样做的时候，不要灰心。
Okay, now let's talk about major scales,
好的，现在让我们来谈谈大调音阶，
remember our major scale,
记得我们的大调音阶，
it is pattern of half steps and whole steps,
它是半音和全音的模式，
what's the pattern,
是什么模式，
two wholes and a half,
两个全音，一个半音，
whole whole half,
全音，全音，半音，
then three wholes and a half,
然后三个全音，一个半音，
whole, whole step, whole step, half,
全音，全音，全音，半音，
put that all together,
把所有这些放在一起，
whole step, whole step, half step, whole step, whole step, whole step, half step,
全音，全音，半音，全音，全音，全音，半音，
let's play or let's spell it in G,
让我们演奏或拼写它在 G 大调中，
if we were in G,
我们在 G 中，
G, now I need a whole step, that's A,
G ，现在我需要一个全音，那是 A ，
now need another whole step, B,
现在需要另一个全音， B ，
now I need a half step, C,
现在我需要一个半音， C ，
I need a whole step, now, D,
现在我需要一个全音， D ，
I need another whole step, E
我需要另一个全音， E ，
and now I need a third whole step,
现在我需要第三个全音，
which that's going to make that an #F,
也就是 #F ，
E to #F
E 到 #F ，
and then I need a half step at the end, #F to G,
最后我需要一个半音， #F 到 G ，
so G scale is G A B C D E #F G,
所以 G 调是 G A B C D E #F G ，
we learn about keys and key signatures next time,
我们下一次学习调和调号，
but that #F is telling you some very important information,
但是 #F 会告诉你一些非常重要的信息，
in the key of G, we have an #F.
在 G 调中，我们有一个 #F 。
Let's do one more,
让我们再做一个，
let's spell a bB scale,
让我们拼写一个 bB 调，
starts on a bB,
从 bB 开始，
then I need a whole step above a bB, should be C,
然后我需要在 bB 上高一个全音，应该是 C ，
I need another whole step, D,
我需要另一个全音， D ，
now I need a half step, up from a D, that would be an bE,
现在我需要从 D 上升半音，这将是 bE ，
so far, I've got bB C D bE,
到目前为止，我得到了 bB C D bE ，
now I need a whole step, to an F,
现在我需要一个全音，到 F ，
another whole step, to a G,
另一个全音，到 G ，
another whole step, the third whole step, that would be to an A,
另一个全音，第三个全音，到 A ，
and then our half step at the end,
然后最后的半音，
gets us back to bB where we started,
让我们回到开始的 bB ，
so bB scale is
所以 bB 调是，
bB C D bE F G A bB.
bB C D Eb F G A bB 。
I would encourage you to spell the scales that we have in the worksheets there,
我鼓励你拼写我们在那里的工作表中的调，
if you haven't done so already,
如果你还没有这样做的话，
once you've done them,
一旦你做了它们，
it's not like you've solved the problem,
这并不是说你已经解决了问题，
once you do go back and do them again,
一旦你回去再做一次，
so write down, I would write down on a piece of paper,
我会在一张纸上写下来，
C F, all the different keys should have twelve of them by the time you're done
C F ，当你做完的时候，所有不同的调都应该有 12 个，
and then write out those major scales again
然后再写出那些大调音阶，
and write them out again and write them out again
再一次写下它们，再一次写下它们，
until you can memorize that bB scale has bB and bE in it,
直到你记住 bB 调有 bB 和 bE ，
and a G scale has an #F in it,
G 调中有 #F ，
now it may seem like a lot of information
现在它可能看起来像是大量的信息，
and it is a lot of information,
而且是大量的信息，
but it's like your multiplication tables,
但这就像你的乘法表，
you just kind of have to memorize them,
你只是必须记住它们，
because where we're going, it's going to take,
因为我们要去的地方，
you're going to need that information quickly and readily,
你会很快和容易地需要这些信息，
so I encourage you to,
所以我鼓励你，
if you need to stop everything now,
如果你现在需要停止一切，
don't go on,
不要继续，
until you memorize those scales,
直到你记住那些音阶，
and what sharps and flats go with those,
那些有什么升调和降调，
we'll talk more about the keys next time,
我们下一次会更多地讨论调，
it's very hard work added,
这是非常困难的工作，
but you can do it,
但你可以做到，
learning music is a big task
学习音乐是一项艰巨的任务，
and not very many people delve into actually understanding what they're playing,
没有多少人真正深入了解他们演奏的是什么，
that's what separates the average player from going beyond average,
这是普通演奏者与超出平均水平的演奏者的区别，
so I'm glad you've chosen to do that,
所以我很高兴你选择这样做，
so we'll see you next time.
所以我们下一次再见。